♪〜
I want to talk...
About your Wonderful Original
Interviews with Monster Girls
The class is astir
I want to let myself go too,
But I end up putting on a fake smile.
Your eyes alone conveyed a competitive spirit
Biting at your lip forcefully.
You once said,
"I wouldn't want to worry what someone thinks
And end up hurting someone else in the process!"
When the chime rings out, as the rain lifts up,
We'll pass the boundaries of our school!
Jumping through the puddles, light will scatter about
Our smiles, and wishes will be so bright!
I want to talk...
About your Wonderful Original!
〜♪
（アラーム音）
Ms. Succubus Is a Real Adult
（早紀絵(さきえ)）んっ
んん…
（早紀絵）んん…
I am Satou Sakie.
（早紀絵）
私は佐藤(さとう)早紀絵
The math teacher at Shibasaki Prefectural High School.
県立 柴崎(しばさき)高等学校 数学教師
I'm 24 and single.
24歳 独身
My mornings start early.
私の朝は早い
Today's horoscope for Aquarius looks positive.
（テレビ音声）
みずがめ座の
今日の運勢は晴れ
Be assertive and don't fear change,
変化を恐れず
攻めの姿勢で
恋のチャンス到来の予感
and a chance for love might come your way!
Next, for Pisces...
次に 魚座のあなた…
A chance for love, huh?
恋のチャンスね
I can't even hope for a decent relationship.
（早紀絵）
まともな恋愛なんて
私には望むべくもない
Because I'm...
なぜなら 私が…
a succubus.
サキュバスだから
ハア〜 あっ
（男）ん？
（早紀絵）フッ フフフ… フ〜ン
That was close...
危なかった
The first two-car train to Shibasaki will arrive momentarily.
（構内アナウンス）
まもなく 柴崎行き始発電車が
２両編成で参ります
Please wait behind the yellow line.
黄色い線の内側に下がって
お待ちください
（戸が開く音）
はっ
Good morning, Ms. Satou.
（校長）
おはようございます 佐藤先生
（早紀絵）
あっ ああ…
おはようございます
O-O-Oh... Good morning!
You're always the first one here, and you even clean up.
いつも 一番に来て
そのうえ 掃除までしてくださって
Thank you for all of your effort.
本当に ご苦労さまです
Oh, no, it's nothing.
いえいえ そんな
私 お掃除が好きなんですよ アハッ
I just really enjoy cleaning!
Actually, it's because I arrived so early, I had nothing better to do.
（早紀絵）
本当は早く来過ぎて
することがないからだ
Oh, Ms. Satou...
（女子）あっ 佐藤先生
（早紀絵）おはよう
Good morning.
Good morning!
（女子たち）おはようございます
Morning, Mr. Takahashi!
（ひかり）先生 おはよう！
（高橋(たかはし)）おう おはよう
Hey, morning.
（ひかり）もっと 元気よく！
Now with more energy!
Good morning!
（高橋）おはようございます！
（ひかり）合格！
You pass!
It's still morning, and yet you're so hyper.
（高橋）朝から テンション高いな
Yeah, I guess.
（ひかり）まあね〜
By the way, thanks.
あっ そうそう
（ひかり）先生 ありがとね
（高橋）ん？
Hmm?
For getting approval for Macchi's backpack!
マッチーのリュックの件
頼んでくれて
ああ いや
感謝するのは むしろこっちだ
Nah, I'm the one who should thank you.
I should have thought of it first.
本当は俺が先に気付くべきだった
I didn't mean to say that so forcefully.
（早紀絵）
あんなに強く言うつもりはなかった
はう！　ハア…
But I can't carelessly come into contact with a man.
（早紀絵）
でも 男性と気軽に
接触するわけにはいかない
That is because I'm a succubus.
なぜなら 私は サキュバスだから
（チャイム）
Ms. Satou...
（女子）佐藤先生
Yes?
（早紀絵）なあに？
I'm having trouble with this problem.
（女子）この問題なんですけど
Ah, for this, you use the formula I taught you today. See?
（早紀絵）
ああ ここは
今日教えた式を使って… ねっ
Oh, I get it!
（女子）
ああ 分かりました
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
You need to know the sin and cos values,
and also how to find them...
（早紀絵）
サイン コサインの値は
丸暗記しないで導き方を覚えて…
What's wrong?
どうしたの？
You're so pretty.
（女子）
先生 すごくきれい
もっと おしゃれしたらいいのに
You should dress up more.
I don't need to do things like that.
私は そういうの大丈夫だから
I see.
そうですか
If you have any more trouble, just ask me.
（早紀絵）
また 分からないところがあったら
聞いてね
I will. Thank you.
はい ありがとうございます
I can't dress up because...
（早紀絵）
おしゃれなんてできない
なぜなら…
It'd have an aphrodisiac effect!
催淫(さいいん)してしまうから
Aphrodisiac effects mesmerize others, sexually arousing them.
（早紀絵）
催淫は相手を魅了し
性欲を高進させること
Succubi are demis with the capacity to
cause aphrodisiac effects on men.
サキュバスは
男性を催淫してしまう性質を持つ
デミなのだ
However, succubi have self-control.
だが サキュバスは自制が利く
By dressing and carrying ourselves so
as to avoid evoking sexual thoughts,
なるべく 性を想起させない
身なり 振る舞いをし
and keeping a good head on our shoulders at all times...
常に気を確かに持つことで…
Just try and say that again!
（太田(おおた)）
もういっぺん 言ってみろ！
（早紀絵）あっ
（佐竹(さたけ)）ああ！
What's wrong, Satake?
（太田）どうした 佐竹？
なんか めっちゃエロい人に
当たった気がしたんだが…
For a second, I felt like I bumped into someone really sexy...
What overly specific feeling is that?
（太田）なんだ その具体的な感覚
But... If I remember right, Ms. Satou is a succubus!
（佐竹）
ああ… でも 佐藤先生って
確か サキュバス…
（太田）え？
Huh?
And if anything does happen,
（早紀絵）
万が一の場合も この程度で済む
this is the extent of it.
Still...
とはいえ…
To avoid the dangerous rush hours,
危険なラッシュを避けるため
行きは始発 帰りは終電間近
I take the day's first and last trains.
It's rough to wake so early and get home late every day.
毎日の早朝 深夜通勤は つらい
I'm getting pretty tired...
だいぶ疲れが たまってるな
いけない 気をつけないと
N-No, I have to be careful.
（男）あっ
（男）ああ！
What the heck's wrong with you?
（女）ちょっと何？　どうしたの？
（早紀絵）あ…
I just had a super sexy dream!
（男）今 めっちゃ エロい夢見た
Huh? What the hell? I don't get you.
（女）
はあ？
何それ 意味分かんない
When I'm asleep, I can't control myself,
so I end up giving others obscene dreams.
（早紀絵）
自制の利かない睡眠時は
他者に淫靡(いんび)な夢を見せてしまう
That's why succubi are also called "dream demons."
サキュバスが夢魔(むま)とも呼ばれる
ゆえんだ
Damn...
しまった
For that reason,
（早紀絵）
よって 私は
アパート マンション等の
I can't live in an apartment building or a complex housing many people.
集合住宅に住むことは
できないのだ
I'm home...
（早紀絵）ただいま
I was prepared for this,
覚悟はしていたけど
but it really is hard for a succubus to live a decent life in a normal society.
サキュバスが社会で
まっとうに生きるのは大変だな
結婚して家庭に入れば
落ち着いて生活できるのかな？
If I married and had a family, could I have a more relaxed life?
Marriage.
結婚…
フッ 笑っちゃう
Now, that's funny.
I've never even had a real relationship, at my age.
いい年して
まともな恋愛すらしたことない私が
Marriage isn't going to happen.
結婚だなんて
As a succubus, it probably wouldn't be hard
（早紀絵）
恐らく サキュバスである
私にとって
for me to build what society would call a romantic relationship.
世間でいう恋愛関係を構築するのは
難しくない
If I walked outside in some flashy clothes,
それこそ派手な格好をして
外を歩けば
the opposite sex would notice and flock to me.
異性は好意を持って やって来る
But I don't think that's true romance,
ただ それは
本当の恋愛ではないと思う
and their interest would be fake.
その好意はニセモノだと
But when I fall in love with a man,
でも 私が異性を好きになったとき
is that feeling any different from what men feel toward me?
その気持ちは
異性が私を思う気持ちと
何か異なるのだろうか？
If it really isn't different at all...
何も違わないとするのならば…
プハ〜！　おいしい〜！
That's so good!
The only time I can stretch my wings is when I'm at home!
羽を伸ばせるのは
家にいるときだけだもんね
Okay! Let's pop open another!
よ〜し もう１本 開けるか
Yahoo!
イ〜ヤッホ〜イ！
デゥフ〜イ ハハ〜
（犬の遠ぼえ）
（アラーム音）
Today's horoscope for Libra is favorable.
（テレビ音声）
てんびん座の運勢は快晴
（あくび）
Guess I got carried away and drank too much.
調子に乗って 飲み過ぎたかな
No, no! I can't doze off at school—
ダメダメ
学校で うたた寝だけは避けないと
うわっ
Are you all right, Ms. Satou?
大丈夫ですか？　佐藤先生
Mr. Takahashi—
高橋先生
はっ うわ〜！
Th-Thank you! I-I'm sorry! Um, I mean...
ありがとうございます
すっ すみません
（早紀絵）あっ あの その…
（高橋）ん？
うう… ん？
アハハ お疲れみたいですね
You seem pretty tired.
Your students are important, but take care of yourself, too.
生徒のことも大事ですが
ご自愛もなさってください
R-Right. Thank you...
は… はい
ありがとうございます
We just touched, right?
今 触ったよね
And yet he's so calm...
なのに あんな平然と…
I'd never thought about it.
（早紀絵）
考えたこともなかった
If it's a succubus's nature to arouse sexual desire,
性欲の高進が
サキュバスの性質なら
maybe it has less effect on people without
strong sexual desires in the first place?
もともと性的な欲の浅い人は
その影響を受けづらいのでは？
Maybe in terms of romance,
that puts us on even footing.
恋愛において
対等な立場にあるのでは？
This has never happened before.
こんなの初めて
Who would think that these disregarded reactions
変だな
脈なしと思える反応ほど
would be the ones making my heart race even faster.
胸が高鳴るなんて…
（高橋）だっ ハア ハア…
ハア ハア…
うう…
Damn, succubi are so erotic!
サキュバス めっちゃ エロいな
平静を保ててよかった
Thank god I was able to keep my cool...
The biology teacher, Takahashi Tetsuo,
（ひまり）
生物教師 高橋鉄男(てつお)は
Interviews with Monster Girls
is a natural lady-killer.
天然のたらしである
So erotic...
（高橋）
エロいな〜
"Succubus, also called 'dream demon.'
（高橋）
サキュバス 淫魔(いんま)とも呼ばれる—
Demi-humans with the capacity to
cause an aphrodisiac effect on others.
相手を催淫してしまう
性質を持つ亜人(あじん)
I've also met a vampire, a dullahan, and a snow woman.
そのほかにも
バンパイア デュラハンに雪女と
All of these, in such a short time."
この短期間に
さまざまなデミと出会った
（戸が開く音）
Mr. Takahashi, let me cool down!
（ひかり）先生 涼ませて〜
ハア〜
You still can't stand sunlight, huh?
相変わらず 日の光は苦手か？
Well, it's been getting hotter and hotter lately, you know?
う〜ん
最近どんどん暑くなるでしょ？
一日中 当たるのは つらいよ
Being stuck in it for the whole day is tough...
What're ya looking at?
先生 何見てるの？
Whoa, it's too hot for this!
暑苦しい
涼みに来たんじゃなかったのか？
Didn't you come here to cool down?
何これ ばあむぴれ？
What is this?
"Vam... pi... re"?
（高橋）バンパイアだ
That's "vampire."
Oh, an article about me?
（ひかり）あっ 私の項目？
Yep, about your reaction to light, preferred diet,
（高橋）
そうそう
日の光のこと 食の好み
necessity of sucking blood, and the
stuff about crosses and garlic, too.
血を吸うことの必要性
十字架やニンニクについても
語ったな
I wrote about a lot of things...
ともあれ
まあ いろいろと語ったもんだ
個人的には
Personally,
I was particularly interested in the link
between bloodsucking and romance.
吸血行動と恋愛間の関係が
興味深かった
うっ… 恋愛？
R-Romance?
Oh, sorry... I guess I shouldn't have said that.
ああ　すまん すまん
あんまり言わないほうが
よかったか
やっぱり恥ずかしいよな
It must be embarrassing, huh?
（ひかり）
べ… 別に 全然！
むしろ語り足りないくらいですよ
N-No... Not at all!
In fact, I can't stop talking about it!
Really?
いいの？
Then, since you offered, I'll ask.
じゃあ せっかくだから聞くけどさ
I've heard that bloodsucking has sexual undertones for vampires,
吸血って バンパイアにとって
性的なニュアンスも含んだ
行為らしいけど
それって どれくらいなのかなって
but how far does it go?
H-How far?!
（ひかり）どっ どれくらい？
Y-You mean, like...
つ… つまり その…
キ… キッスと比べてどうかとか
そういうこと？
compared to k-kissing... and such?
That sort of thing?
That's right.
そうそう
例えば キス以上とか
Is it more than a kiss, but less than sex?
セックス未満とか
（ひかり）セ！
Se—
Sex. Sex.
（高橋:エコーのかかった声で）
セックス セックス セックス…
Sex...
I-I-I'd say...
（ひかり）
セ… ス…
ひ… 人それぞれ ではないかと
It depends on the person.
Well, sure, but I'd like to know your personal thoughts.
（高橋）いや そうなんだが
お前自身の考えを
聞きたいんだけどな
B-But I've never had any romantic experiences!
だっ だって
私 恋愛経験ないし…
それは知ってる
I know that.
And I've only sucked someone's blood once.
人から血を吸ったことも
１回しかないし
But everyone's seen a scene like that in movies, right?
でも ドラマや映画で
そういうシーン見るだろ？
それと比べて… あっ
Compared to that, is it—
あっ… ああ そう
Oh, right!
Of course... It depends on the person, right?
そうだよな 人それぞれだよな
Bloodsucking began as a practice to let
vampires, who tend to be low on blood,
もともと吸血は
血が不足しがちな
バンパイア特有の体質を
supplement their own with that of others.
他者から補う習慣だったわけだが
But now, you receive blood from the government,
今は国から血液が支給されるから
そもそも吸う必要はない
so it's no longer necessary.
Naturally, you'd value it less.
そりゃあ 価値観もまばらになる
Th-That's right!
そ… そうだね
Wait a minute...
ん？　待てよ？
ということは
Does that mean categorizing bloodsucking
as sexual is wrong, in and of itself?
吸血を性的なカテゴリー内だけで
線引きすること自体 間違いか
In terms of traditional culture,
which contemporary people may be losing,
人によっては失われつつある
伝統的な文化として
maybe that behavior has a value that doesn't compare to sex...
セックスと比べられない
価値のある行為なのかもしれない
T-Two times!
（ひかり）にっ ２回目？
むむむ…
And I'm trying so hard to not show how embarrassed I am.
こっちは恥ずかしいのが
バレないように頑張ってるのに
あっ
（高橋）ん？
うん？
（ひかり）あのね あのね
Hey, hey...
ちゅっ
ヒヒヒ〜 引っ掛かった〜
Gotcha!
Maybe kissing is easier than sucking blood!
血を吸うより
キスのほうが簡単かもね
ん？
フッ
I see, I see.
なるほど なるほど
"Kissing is easier than sucking blood."
“血を吸うより
キスのほうが簡単”と
（ひかり）うわっ メモるな！
Don't write that down!
And show a little embarrassment, would you?
ていうか 少しは照れてよ〜
（高橋）
この子には まだ早いようだが
Looks like she's still too young for this,
Come on! Are you listening?
but I wonder what sort of perspective demis actually have on romance.
そもそも デミの恋愛観とは
一体
どういったものなのだろうか？
（早紀絵）
町(まち)さんの担任も気付かない人ね
I guess your homeroom teacher isn't very attentive, Machi.
Honestly, making you carry this box all by yourself...
荷物運びを
あなた 一人に任せるなんて
Sorry about this, Ms. Satou.
（町）すみません 佐藤先生
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
いいのよ 気にしないで
Reference Room
Confessions of a Mask
Machi, this book goes on that shelf, too.
町さん この本もそっちの棚みたい
お願いできる？
Can you handle it?
S-Sure.
あっ はい
あの… 佐藤先生って
Um, Ms. Satou...
Yes?
なあに？
You give off the impression of being a very mature woman.
大人の女性って感じですよね
（早紀絵）フッ どうしたの 急に？
Where did that come from?
You're beautiful and kind.
きれいだし 優しいし
I imagine you have a lot of romantic experience, too.
きっと恋愛経験も
豊富なんでしょうね
（早紀絵）え？
（町）ん？
W-Well...
まっ まあ 多少はね
More or less.
Actually, I wanted your advice about something.
（町）
実は相談したいことがありまして
ん？
I, um...
私 その…
好きな人がいるんです
I have someone I like.
Oh, you do? That's so nice!
あら そうなの　ステキね
相手は この学校の生徒？
Is it a student at this school?
N-No, he is part of this school, but...
（町）
いっ いえ
うちの学校の人ではあるんですが
ん？
I...
わっ 私…
高橋先生のことが好きなんです
I like Mr. Takahashi!
Me too!
私も好き
あっ 日下部(くさかべ)…
Kusakabe—
（佐竹）日下部
Kusakabe!
（雪(ゆき)）あっ
On our next day off, wanna hang out?
（佐竹）
よかったら
今度の休み 遊びに行かね？
Huh? N-No, I'll pass on that.
え？　わっ 私はいいよ
そういうの
Come on, come on! Just this once!
（佐竹）
いいじゃん いいじゃん
たまにはさ〜
Really, I'll pass...
ホントに大丈夫だから 私は
Sorry.
（雪）ごめんね
（佐竹）あ…
H-Hey...
（女子）アハハハ
（高橋）とう
（佐竹）あたっ
Ow!
Ouch!
（高橋）てい
（太田）おたっ
（佐竹）
って〜
なんで たたくんだよ テツ先生
Why did you hit us, teach?
I was trying to talk to Kusakabe.
俺が日下部に
話しかけようと思ってたのに
And you just took that out on us?
そんな八つ当たりみたいな
理由で？
とんでもねえな この人
This guy's unbelievable.
Sorry... The thing is that I've tried talking to her several times,
すまん すまん
いやな 実は
何度か日下部に話しかけたんだが
ことごとく逃げられてしまってな
but she keeps running away from me.
Hmm...
（佐竹）ふ〜ん
Wouldn't she come if you called her on the PA?
（太田）
放送で呼び出したら
さすがに来るんじゃ
Well, I just want to talk to her out of personal interest.
いや まあ
個人的に聞きたいことだしな
So I know being too persistent is a bad approach, but...
だから 余計に
しつこくするのもよくないんだが
う〜ん
（女子）えっ なに？
（男子）どうした？
What's wrong with him?
う〜ん
（男子）どうしたの？
（女子）なに なに？
What? What's up?
（高橋）
相手は年頃の女の子だし
とやかく聞くのは野暮(やぼ)…
But she is a teenage girl.
Asking her too many questions
might be insensitive...
He's mumbling to himself.
（太田）
なんか
ぶつぶつ言ってる
Mr. Tetsu is so weird...
（佐竹）
テツ先生
変わってるよな
I don't mind it, though.
嫌いじゃないけど
O-Oh?
（早紀絵）
へっ へえ〜 そうなんだ…
You do?
Wait, why make this a competition?
って張り合ってどうする？
彼女は生徒 私は教師
She's a student, and I'm a teacher!
Th-That's surprising.
い… 意外ねえ
それで 相談っていうのは？
So what did you want my advice about?
Oh, right, about that...
（町）あっ はい
それなんですが
高橋先生と釣り合うには
I'm worried I might be a little too...
well, childish for Mr. Takahashi.
私は その…
子供っぽすぎるなって…
I want to be more mature,
大人っぽくなりたいと思っても
but I don't know what that truly means.
具体的にそれが どういうことか
分からなくて…
That's why you asked me?
それで 私に？
I-I'm not sure how to put it, but I see you
う… うまく言えませんが
佐藤先生は私の中で
as the embodiment of an attractive, mature woman.
かっこいい大人の女性
そのものって感じで
And you look like you'd have a lot of experience, too.
恋愛経験も
豊富そうに見えるので…
O-Oh...
そっ そう
本当に見えるだけなんだけどね
Actually, I only look that way.
ん？
But you know, Machi...
（早紀絵）
でもね 町さん
大人って案外大したことないものよ
Adults really aren't all that impressive.
I'm sorry if this sounds like I'm saying you're just a child,
こういう言い方は あなたを
子供扱いしているみたいで悪いけど
but a lot of the "maturity" that kids see is just a facade.
子供から見える大人っぽさって
結構 建て前なのよ
A facade?
建て前ですか？
Yes, we want to appear admirable to society.
そう
社会的に立派に見られたい
We want kids to respect us.
子供に尊敬されたい
It's a facade meant to achieve that.
それを達成するための建て前
I guess adults really are pretty vain.
見えっ張りなのかな 大人は
Especially ones who do this kind of work.
こういう仕事してる人は特にね
かっこつけたくなっちゃう
We want to look good.
Is that true for you, as well?
佐藤先生も そうなんですか？
（早紀絵）ウフフフ
Who can say?
それは どうかしらね？
Yes, it is!
（早紀絵）
そうです！
たっ 高橋先生も？
M-Mr. Takahashi, too?
Hmm... We are both adults, but he and I
（早紀絵）う〜ん
同じ社会人でも
私と高橋先生って
are about as many years apart as you and I.
あなたと私くらい
年が離れているから…
でも 少なくとも言えることは
But the one thing I can say
is that Mr. Takahashi looks very mature to me, too.
私から見ても
高橋先生は大人に見えるわ
He seems relaxed and carefree,
自然体で のんびりしているようで
頼もしくて
but he's very reliable.
He's able to connect openly with anyone,
誰にでも気さくに接せられるけど
踏み込み過ぎて傷つけはしない
but he doesn't push too far and end up hurting you.
I think it's pretty impressive.
ああ すごいなあって
かっこいいな〜って
And really attractive.
（町）ほ〜
（早紀絵）はっ
B-By the way, what is it you like about Mr. Takahashi?
ち… ちなみに町さんは
高橋先生の
どういうところが好きなのかしら？
Well...
えっと 佐藤先生も
おっしゃっていましたが
Just like you said,
I guess I like how nice and dependable he is.
やっぱり優しいところとか
頼れるところとか
分かる
I get you.
Also, I like how strong his arms are.
（町）
あと腕のがっちりした感じとか
I totally get you!
すごく分かる！
（町）ほ〜
（早紀絵）はあっ！
S-So on that note,
そ… そういうわけで
見た目から始めるのはどうかしら？
why not start with your appearance?
ファッションとか
ヘアスタイルとか
Like with fashion or your hairstyle?
R-Right, that might be a good idea.
そ… そうですね
それが いいかもしれません
Oh, but as for my hair...
ああ でも 髪型は…
I, um, can't grow my hair out long.
私 その…
髪を長くできないんです
It gets slippery, so it's dangerous.
あまり長いと
滑ったりして危ないから
あっ そうか　ごめんなさい
気が付かなくて
Oh, I see! I'm sorry, I didn't notice!
I-It's okay. I can't grow it out, but I can change the style.
い… いえ 長くはできなくても
髪型は変えられるので
Oh, but when I spoke to Mr. Takahashi about it...
あっ でも
この話を高橋先生にしたとき…
Hmm, really?
へえ そうか
Well, I'm glad you're a dullahan, though.
いや しかし
町が デュラハンでよかった
え？
We sort of match. Isn't that cool?
おそろいみたいで
いいじゃないか
Isn't that cool?
（高橋）
いいじゃないか…
Isn't that cool?
He said that, and it made me so happy,
って言ってくれて
それが うれしかったから
I felt like I wouldn't mind keeping this style forever...
ずっと同じ髪型でもいいかなって
そう思って…
Ms. Satou?
先生？
That sounds nice.
（早紀絵）いいな
（町）え？
That sounds nice...
いいな〜
That sounds so nice!
いいな〜 それ
なんか その髪型みたいなやつ
Like, what, having matching hairstyles?!
そういう なんか
おそろいみたいな…
First Love
And this?
（早紀絵）これは？
（町）あっ ２段目です
First Love
The second shelf.
Okay.
（早紀絵）はい
I am Satou Sakie.
（早紀絵）
私は佐藤早紀絵
And this?
100 Years of Solitude
（早紀絵）これは？
（町）それも２段目です
100 Years of Solitude
Also the second shelf.
（早紀絵）はい
Okay.
The math teacher at Shibasaki High School.
（早紀絵）
柴崎高等学校 数学教師
The Agony of Coming
Into the World
And...
The Agony of Coming
Into the World
（早紀絵）これ…
（町）２段目です
The Agony of Coming
Into the World
Second shelf.
The Agony of Coming
Into the World
（早紀絵）ハア…
I'm 24 and single.
（早紀絵）
24歳 独身
ハア〜
Despite all this, I'm a real adult.
（早紀絵）
これでも いい大人である
ハア…
Oh, and listen to this. At lunch today...
（木村(きむら)）ああ でさ〜 聞いて？
（木村）今日の昼休みさ
（井森(いもり)）うん
Uh-huh?
Satake, from class A, was hitting on a girl in the hall.
（木村）
Ａ組の佐竹ってヤツが
廊下で口説いてたの
（井森）マジ？
For real?
He needs to think about where he is.
場所わきまえろっての
ちなみに相手 誰？
Who was the girl, anyway?
Oh, that one chick...
（木村）
ああ あいつ　Ａ組の日下部
Kusakabe, from class A.
Oh, her?
（井森）ああ あいつか〜
フフッ あいつさ
ちょっと調子に乗ってない？
She's looks kinda arrogant, don't you think?
Yeah.
（木村）ああ それ 私も思った
Right?
（井森）やっぱり？
（木村）思う 思う
Totally.
I mean, she is cute, but...
（井森）まあ 確かに かわいいよ
（木村）そうだね
Yeah.
I admit she is cute,
（井森）
かわいいのは認めるけどさ
遊びくらい行ってやってもいいのに
but she could hang out with him once, at least.
Maybe she thinks she's some kind of idol...
（木村）
アイドルにでも
なったつもりなのかね
Wouldn't an idol try to make a better impression?
（井森）
アイドルなら
もっと外面 良くするんじゃない？
Yeah, true!
（木村）ああ 言えてる
（２人の笑い声）
Bye, teach!
先生 さようなら
Yep, bye.
はい さようなら
With more energy!
（ひかり）もっと元気よく
Goodbye!
さようなら〜！
You pass! You may go!
合格！　帰ってよし
Not having a care in the world must be nice.
お前 悩み なさそうでいいな
Yeah, I guess...
（ひかり）まあね〜 じゃあね〜
See ya!
Be careful on your way home!
気をつけて帰れよ
Okay!
（ひかり）は〜い
What is this?
何だ？
何か ひんやりとした空気が…
The air feels kind of chilly.
Kusakabe?
（高橋）日下部？
（雪）はっ
あ…
Mr. Takahashi...
先生
♪〜
The events of a mysterious world,
Like the ones you hear of in fairy tales,
Are actually closer than you think
Just like the way you and I met!
When I stood up tall to gaze at
The familiar scenery outside my window,
Even days that felt like torture seemed precious somehow.
Stuck in my heart, I can't put them into words
How should I try to put these feelings into words?
Laughing over stupid things...
Getting mad over small details...
We'll keep carving these trivial moments into our hearts.
Sometimes I'm feeling sad...
But when I'm with you, I'm so happy!
We'll keep on building these irreplaceable moments,
And little by little, we'll come to understand one another.
〜♪
Next Time
Takahashi Tetsuo Wants to Protect
Next time on Interviews with Monster Girls:
（ひまり）
次回「亜人ちゃんは
語りたい」
Takahashi Tetsuo Wants to Protect.
「高橋鉄男は守りたい」